BRIDGET WILLIAMS

DESIGNER, ILLUSTRATOR + BRAND STRATEGIST

CONTACT

719.966.9991

bridgetwdesigns.com

bridgetw.designs@gmail.com

HELLO

I am a graphic designer with 10+ years of experience using the Adobe Creative Suite, managing brands and creating beautiful, effective design solutions for print and digital marketing across multi-media platforms, and I would like to work for you.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe Photoshop Adobe Acrobat After Effects Adobe XD Fiama Microsoft 365 Square Space Canva Google Suite

PRO SKILLS

Project Management **Design Thinking** Branding Illustration Typography Color Theory Wire Framing Photo Editing Animation Asset Organization Time Management Collaborating Communication Presenting Learning new systems Incorporating feedback

EDUCATION

Portland Community College AAS: Graphic Design

Michigan Tech University

BFA: Fine Art

WORK EXPERIENCE

Gibbs Smith | Senior Designer | May 2021-Present

- Create engaging and well-organized layouts and templates for printed and digital educational materials.
- Collaborate with educators, curriculum developers, editors, and other designers to ensure consistent branding across multi-media projects and products that elevate our brand messaging.
- Compose text, imagery, and photography to communicate concepts that inspire, inform, and engage target audiences.
- · Lead a team of designers to ensure that project deadlines are met, brand guidelines are consistently elevated and files are organized.
- · Mentor junior designers.

BCI Media | Lead Designer + Brand Strategist | March 2020-May 2021

- Designed and delivered print publications, social media graphics, pitch decks, event branding, and other multi-media assets that satisfied client needs and exceeded expectations.
- Produced social media templates, print and digital ads, and branded landing pages based on current trends and impactful iterative design.
- Partnered effectively with marketing managers and stakeholders to plan and execute campaigns and rebrands.
- · Analyzed customer needs, marketing opportunities, and working contexts, then synthesized research insights to inform design decisions and create visualizations that effectively targeted key findings.

RP Creative | Designer + Content Specialist | Oct. 2018–March 2020

- Imagined and developed beautiful branding including logos, typography and color pallets based on deep understanding of client briefs.
- Leveraged and evolved brand standards to reflect dynamic changes in messaging, offerings, and events.
- Developed innovative design for products and packaging, marketing, emails campaigns and social media based on relevant design trends.
- Created wire-frames, flow diagrams, mock-ups, and high-fidelity prototypes to communicate future user interface and experience.
- Effectively communicated with outside partners to ensure high quality asset transfer and successful project resolution.
- Conceptualized characters and environments for illustration and brought projects through to completion.

Glick and Fray | Illustrator | July 2022–Present

• Create Illustrations for product design and marketing campaigns.